We are going to talk about the different products that make framing molding.
One of the things that they use as wood they use several different kinds of wood.
Mostly every wood out there.
It is hard to determine what each one is without really knowing your woods.
This happens to be a piece of oak, it is very hard, it is very not, it is hard to destroy, it is hard to dent, it is hard to chip.
You can tell it is wood by looking at the edge of it here.
You can tell that it is wood by looking at the back of it.
If you look at this one, you can tell this one is not wood and that this is.
Wood is something that is going to give you a long life, a shelf life.
It is going to hang around for many years to come.
When I say many years at least a hundred, if it is taking care of properly.